In this clip, I will keep introducing to you other steps of the dance Ruchenitza.
The one which is called scissoring.
The legs are moving forward, sliding, with the same count.
Three, one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three.
We can walk forward or in place or backwards.
We can move sideways.
Three, one, two, three.
But always keep the bouncing.
Two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three.
The tempo goes different.
One, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three.
Now we will combine the basic movement, the cross step and the scissoring.
One, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three.